const data=[
    {
        "question": "WHY SMIRA CLUB?",
        "answer":" WE OFFER CHOICE, VALUE, FLEXIBILITY, KNOWLEDGE EXPERTISE ALL  AT THE BEST PRICE. WE ARE EXTREMELY CONFIDENT THAT WE OFFER COMPETITIVE PRICE, SO WE HAVE OUR PRICE MATCH PROMISE. ALL OUR STAFF CONTINUALLY TRAINED TO IMPROVE THEIR SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE  OUR TEAMS ARE PASSIONATE, ENTHUSIASTIC AND FRIENDLY. WE STRIVE TO BE AHEAD OF OUR INDUSTRY, OFTEN LEADING THE WAY."
    },
    {
        "question":"HOW DO I BOOK MY ACCOMMODATION?",
        "answer":"BOOKING PROCESS IS EASY. CUSTOMER CAN CALL US ON OUR BOOKING NUMBERS 9819812456 / 9833733477 / 9820342389, PROVIDE US WITH MEMBERSHIP DETAILS. BOOKING BASED ON SUBJECT TO HOTEL AVAILABILITY.PRIOR BOOKING IS MANDATORY AS PER THE CUSTOMERS MEMBERSHIP CATEGORY BOOKING WINDOW."
    },{
        "question":"HOW DO I USE OTHER SERVICES?",
        "answer":" KINDLY CALL ON SERVICE PROVIDER NUMBER MENTIONED. BOOKING CAN ALSO BE DONE VIA SMIRA CLUB. KINDLY BOOK YOUR SERVICES ATLEAST 24 HRS PRIOR. FOR HOTELS, BOOKING PERIOD AS PER THE MEMBERSHIP CATEGORY."
    },
    {
        "question":" WHAT DOCUMENTS SHOULD I CARRY?",
        "answer":"A GOVT-APPROVED IDENTITY CARD IS A MUST WHILE CHECKING IN. DRIVING LICENSE, VOTER ID, ADHAAR CARD, PASSPORT / ANY STATES ID CARD. AGE CRITERIA FOR BOOKING 18 AND ABOVE."
    },
    {
        "question":"HOW DO I GIFT / TRANSFER MY ACCOMMODATION TO MY FAMILIES and FRIENDS.",
        "answer":"THIS SERVICE IS ONLY VALID FOR PLATINUM AND VIP CUSTOMERS. THIS FACILITY CAN ONLY BE AVAILED BY THE HOLIDAY PACKAGE MEMBER. KINDLY NOTE GUEST INFORMATION IS MANDATORY.",
    },{
        "question":"HOW, I CAN UPDATE MY MEMBERSHIP?",
        "answer":"MEMBERSHIP CAN BE UPDATED  ANY TIME DURING THE MEMBERSHIP PERIOD. BY PAYING THE ADDITIONAL UPGRADATION FEES."
    },
    {
        "question":"DO I HAVE TO PAY FOOD CHARGES COMPULSORY?",
        "answer":"YES, (CHARGES TO BE PAID COMPULSORY FOR UNLIMITED BREAKFAST & DINNER) FOR ADULTS 12 YEARS & ABOVE 999 PER PERSON PER NIGHT. FOR 12 YEARS & BELOW 599 PER PERSON PER NIGHT. NO CHARGES FOR 5 YEARS & BELOW."
    },{
        "question":"HOW WILL MY MEMEBERSHIP GETS ACTIVATED?",
        "answer":"MEMBERSHIP WILL GET BE ACTIVATED ON REALTIME BASIC ONCE PAYMENT IS COMPLETED. CUSTOMER WILL RECEIVE A SMS / MAIL IMMEDIATELY. CUSTOMER WILL GET VERIFICATION CALL TO CONFIRM DETAILS WITHIN 24 - 48 HRS."
    },
    {
        "question":"WAS YOUR QUESTION NOT ANSWERED?",
        "answer":"WE ARE HERE TO ASSIST YOU. WRITE TO US AT SUPPORT@SMIRA.CLUB OR CONTACT US ON 9833733477 / 9819812456 / 9820342389."
    },
    {
        "question":" HOW CAN I DO BOOKING ON PEAK DAYS OR WEEKENDS?",
        "answer":"BOOKING ARE NOT VALID FOR BANK HOLIDAYS, PUBLIC HOLIDAYS, LONG WEEKEND. 7 DAYS OF DIWALI AND FROM 24TH DEC. TO 1ST JANUARY. IF CUSTOMER WOULD LIKE TO BOOK ON THE ABOVE MENTIONED DAYS THEN EXTRA AMOUNT WILL BE CHARGED ON PER THE PARTICIPATING SERVICE PROVIDERS RATE POLICY."
    },
    {
        "question":"HOW DO I REGISTER MYSELF ON SMIRA CLUB?",
        "answer":"YOU CAN REGISTER YOURSELF BY CLICKING ON THE 'BUY NOW' TAB ONCE REGISTERED COMPLETE PAYMENT CUSTOMER WILL RECEIVE AN ACTIVATION SMS & EMAIL FORWARDED BY A VERIFICATION CALL TO CONFIRM DETAILS WITHIN 24 - 48 HRS."
    },
    {
        "question":"ARE PET'S ALLOWED IN HOTELS?",
        "answer":"AS PER THE POLICY CUSTOMER SHOULD CLICK WHILE BOOKING CUSTOMER MAY HAVE TO PAY EXTRA CHARGES FOR PET STAY. KINDLY ADHERE TO THE HOTEL NORMS / PET RESTRICTED AREA."
    },
    {
        "question":"WHAT ARE THE ADDITIONAL FEES?",
        "answer":"NO ADDITIONAL FEES, NO MAINTENANCE FEES & NO ANNUAL FEES."
    },
    {
        "question":"WHAT IS THE REFUND POLICY?",
        "answer":"REFUND NOT APPLICABLE ON CANCELLATION OF CONFIRMATION RESERVATION BOOKING OR SERVICES. NO REFUND OR CREDIT WILL BE ISSUED FOR NO SHOW OR NON UTILISED CONFIRMED NIGHTS. CONFIRMED BOOKING / RESERVATION CAN NOT BE TRANSFERRED OR CHANGED."
    },
    {
        "question":"HOW DO I CONTACT CUSTOMER SUPPORT?",
        "answer":"CALL US ON 9833733477 / 9819812456 / 9820342389. EMAIL US AT SUPPORT@SMIRA.CLUB"
    },
    {
        "question":" I HAVE FEEDBACK OR AN IDEA TO SHARE, HOW DO I SHARE IT?",
        "answer":"WE LOVE YOUR FEEDBACK AND IDEA KINDLY SHARE YOUR THOUGHTS / SUGGESTIONS ON SUPPORT@SMIRA.CLUB. YOU CAN ALSO SHARE YOUR REVIEW, FEEDBACK AND RATING ON GOOGLE SMIRA.CLUB "
    }
]
export default data